Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXIV. LOCAL LODGES
  - Sub-Series 235-6192. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6192, Atlantic City Auxiliary Lodge, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1941-1951 (Box 156, Folder 48)
      August 7, 1941-July 25, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6256, Camden, New Jersey, effective 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-6195. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6195, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1942-1946 (Box 156, Folder 49)
      January 30, 1942-November 26, 1946. Suspended, effective November 9, 1946
  - Sub-Series 235-6196. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6196, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1948 (Box 156, Folder 50)
      1948 January 1. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6133, New Orleans, Louisiana, effective January 1, 1948
  - Sub-Series 235-6199. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6199, Atlanta, Georgia, 1946-957 (Box 156, Folder 51)
      February 17, 1946-May 3, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6039, Macon, Georgia, effective January 1, 1957
  - Sub-Series 235-6200. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6200, Montgomery, Alabama, 1942-1957 (Box 156, Folder 52)
      September 30, 1942-January 24, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6162, Montgomery, Alabama, effective October 1, 1956
  - Sub-Series 235-6204. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6204, Hickory Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1944-1958 (Box 156, Folder 53)
      May 23, 1944-June 3, 1958. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6051, Houston, Texas, effective April 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-6206. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6206, Harlem River Lodge, New York, New York, 1942-1946 (Box 156, Folder 54)
      February 4, 1942-February 14, 1946. Suspended, effective December 28, 1945
  - Sub-Series 235-6207. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6207, Washington, D.C., 1947-1956 (Box 156, Folder 55)
      June 25, 1947-March 19, 1956. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6005, Greensboro, North Carolina, effective January 3, 1956
  - Sub-Series 235-6208. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6208, Commissary Employees Lodge, New York, New York, 1942-1946 (Box 156, Folder 56)
      September 10, 1942-October 23, 1946.
  - Sub-Series 235-6210. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6210, Monument Lodge, Danville, Virginia, 1945-1960 (Box 156, Folder 57)
      May 16, 1945-June 2, 1960. Consolidated with Lodges Nos. 6005 and 6006, Greensboro, North Carolina, effective April 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-6215. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6215, Fidelity Lodge, Denver, Colorado, 1943-1953 (Box 156, Folder 58)
      March 19, 1943-August 4, 1953. Consolidated with Lodge No. 87, Denver, Colorado, effective July 1, 1953
  - Sub-Series 235-6216. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6216, Alexandria Lodge, Alexandria, Virginia, 1945-1955 (Box 156, Folder 59)
      October 25, 1945-July 16, 1955.
  - Sub-Series 235-6218. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6218, Poinsett Lodge, Greenville, South Carolina, 1943-1958 (Box 156, Folder 60)
      January 5, 1943-July 28, 1958. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6281, Greenville, South Carolina, effective July 11, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-6220. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6220, Jackson, Tennessee, 1947-1952 (Box 156, Folder 61)
      September 23, 1947-November 11, 1952. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6061, Jackson, Tennessee, effective July 1, 1952
  - Sub-Series 235-6221. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6221, Tyler, Texas, 1947 (Box 156, Folder 62)
      1947 October 3
  - Sub-Series 235-6222. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6222, Columbia, South Carolina, 1944-1947 (Box 156, Folder 63)
      June 21, 1944-February 21, 1947.
  - Sub-Series 235-6223. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6223, Flagger Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1943-1952 (Box 156, Folder 64)
      January 27, 1943-March 20, 1952. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6163, Wilmington, North Carolina, effective February 28, 1952
  - Sub-Series 235-6224. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6224, Stay Right Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1943-1947 (Box 156, Folder 65)
      September 1, 1943-December 1, 1947. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6062, Atlanta, Georgia, effective December 1, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6229. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6229, Somerville, Texas, 1942-1959 (Box 156, Folder 66)
      September 14, 1942-January 21, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1096, Somerville, Texas, effective July 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-6232. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6232, Dixie Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1942-1956 (Box 156, Folder 67)
      December 13, 1942-July 6, 1956. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6010, Atlanta, Georgia, effective June 30, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-6233. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6233, Akron, Ohio, 1945-1952 (Box 156, Folder 68)
      February 28, 1945-October 24, 1952. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1097, Akron, Ohio, effective April 1, 1952
  - Sub-Series 235-6237. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6237, Panhandle Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1942-1947 (Box 156, Folder 69)
      September 29, 1942-September 26, 1947. Formerly Keystone Lodge; suspended, effective February 12, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6238. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6238, St. Louis, Missouri, 1943-1944 (Box 156, Folder 70)
      August 28, 1943-July 10, 1944.
  - Sub-Series 235-6240. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6240, Caswell Lodge, Lenoir, North Carolina, 1942-1948 (Box 156, Folder 71)
      November 7, 1942-December 6, 1948. Moved from Kinston, North Carolina
  - Sub-Series 235-6242. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6242, Chicago Tunnel Auxiliary Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1943-1947 (Box 156, Folder 72)
      August 9, 1943-November 1, 1947. Consolidated with Lodge No. 125, Chicago, Illinois, effective November 1, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6244. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6244, Amarillo Lodge, Amarillo, Texas, 1947-1955 (Box 156, Folder 73)
      August 20, 1947-March 9, 1955. Consolidated with Lodges Nos. 396 and 1079, Amarillo, Texas, effective January 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-6245. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6245, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1943-1944 (Box 156, Folder 74)
      January 18, 1943-March 10, 1944.
  - Sub-Series 235-6247. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6247, Paris, Tennessee, 1943 (Box 156, Folder 75)
      March 16-, 1943.
  - Sub-Series 235-6248. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6248, Erie Railroad Auxiliary Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1943-1947 (Box 156, Folder 76)
      March 12, 1943-November 12, 1947.
  - Sub-Series 235-6249. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6249, Washington, D.C., 1943-1944 (Box 156, Folder 77)
      March 18, 1943-June 4, 1944. Suspended, effective May 18, 1944
  - Sub-Series 235-6250. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6250, Chicago, Illinois, 1943-1954 (Box 156, Folder 78)
      May 18, 1943-January 1, 1954. Consolidated with Lodge No. 241, Chicago, Illinois, effective January 1, 1954
  - Sub-Series 235-6252. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6252, Augusta, Georgia, 1943-1951 (Box 156, Folder 79)
      April 27, 1943-July 5, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6201, Augusta, Georgia, effective July 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-6253. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6253, Zephyr Lodge, Galesburg, Illinois, 1943-1949 (Box 156, Folder 80)
      June 5, 1943-July 1, 1949. Consolidated with Lodge No. 867, Galesburg, Illinois, effective July 1, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-6255. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6255, Kansas City, Missouri, 1945-1955 (Box 156, Folder 81)
      July 7, 1945-October 6, 1955. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1245, Kansas City, Missouri, effective October 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-6256. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6256, Camden Lodge, Camden, New Jersey, 1943-1951 (Box 156, Folder 82)
      August 5, 1943-December 7, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 662, Camden, New Jersey, effective October 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-6258. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6258, Austin Lodge, Durham, North Carolina, 1943-1954 (Box 156, Folder 83)
      September 29, 1943-December 10, 1954. Moved from Raleigh, North Carolina, effective December 9, 1953; suspended, effective August 31, 1954
  - Sub-Series 235-6263. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6263, Hanover Lodge, Wilmington, North Carolina (Box 156, Folder 84)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 6163, Wilmington, North Carolina, effective April 1, 1948
  - Sub-Series 235-6266. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6266, Bus Lodge, Wichita, Kansas, 1944-1949 (Box 156, Folder 85)
      March 13, 1944-April 1, 1949. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1125, Wichita, Kansas, effective April 1, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-6268. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6268, Olympus Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1944-1948 (Box 157, Folder 1)
      April 27, 1944-January 1, 1948. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6180, Cape Charles, Virginia, effective January 1, 1948
  - Sub-Series 235-6269. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6269, St. Louis, Missouri, 1944-1945 (Box 157, Folder 2)
      May 9, 1944-March 29, 1945.
  - Sub-Series 235-6270. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6270, Union Station Lodge, Louisville, Kentucky, 1944-1954 (Box 157, Folder 3)
      May 12, 1944-April 27, 1954. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6236, Louisville, Kentucky, effective April 1, 1954
  - Sub-Series 235-6273. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6273, Rising Sun Auxiliary Lodge, New York, New York, 1944-1947 (Box 157, Folder 4)
      July 7, 1944-December 6, 1947. Consolidated with Lodge No. 657, New York, New York, effective October 1, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6274. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6274, Los Angeles, California, 1944-1947 (Box 157, Folder 5)
      July 15, 1944-September 1, 1947. Consolidated with Lodge No. 30, Los Angeles, California, effective September 1, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6276. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6276, Chicago Union Station Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1944-1947 (Box 157, Folder 6)
      September 7, 1944-September 23, 1947. Consolidated with Lodge No. 342, Chicago, Illinois, effective September 23, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6277. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6277, North Petersburg, Virginia, 1944-1946 (Box 157, Folder 7)
      November 9, 1944-April 19, 1946.
  - Sub-Series 235-6278. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6278, South Cleveland Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1945-1948 (Box 157, Folder 8)
      April 2, 1945-March 12, 1948.
  - Sub-Series 235-6279. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6279, Detroit, Michigan, 1945 (Box 157, Folder 9)
      April 11, 1945-August 15, 1945.
  - Sub-Series 235-6280. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6280, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1945 (Box 157, Folder 10)
      May 17, 1945-November 19, 1945. Suspended, effective November 19, 1945
  - Sub-Series 235-6283. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6283, Dallas, Texas, 1945-1956 (Box 157, Folder 11)
      July 14, 1945-January 1, 1956. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6001, Beaumont, Texas, effective January 1, 1956
  - Sub-Series 235-6284. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6284, Birmingham, Alabama, 1945-1953 (Box 157, Folder 12)
      September 10, 1945-January 7, 1953. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6162, Montgomery, Alabama, effective July 1, 1952
  - Sub-Series 235-6285. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6285, Ancient City Lodge, St. Augustine, Florida, 1945-1950 (Box 157, Folder 13)
      November 15, 1945-October 3, 1950. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6004, Jacksonville, Florida, effective September 19, 1950
  - Sub-Series 235-6288. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6288, Detroit, Michigan, 1945-1959 (Box 157, Folder 14)
      October 8, 1945-January 23, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 168, Detroit, Michigan, effective October 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-6289. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6289, Los Angeles, California, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 15)
      June 26, 1947-September 1, 1947. Consolidated with Lodges Nos. 602, 684, and 929, no location given, effective September 1, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6290. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6290, Twin City Lodge, Bristol, Virginia, 1945-1950 (Box 157, Folder 16)
      October 24, 1945-February 23, 1950. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6168, Roanoke, Virginia, effective October 1, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-6292. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6292, Capitol City Lodge, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1945-1959 (Box 157, Folder 17)
      November 29, 1945-January 1, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 927, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, effective January 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-6294. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6294, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1946-1960 (Box 157, Folder 18)
      January 14, 1946-March 24, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 124, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, effective 1954?
  - Sub-Series 235-6295. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6295, New York, New York, 1946-1955 (Box 157, Folder 19)
      January 28, 1946-October 19, 1955. Consolidated with Lodge No. 70, New York, New York, effective July 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-6297. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6297, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1946-1960 (Box 157, Folder 20)
      March 19, 1946-November 1, 1960. Disbanded, effective May 27, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-6299. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6299, Carver Lodge, New York, New York, 1946-1947 (Box 157, Folder 21)
      April 6, 1946-December 19, 1947.
  - Sub-Series 235-6300. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6300, Greenville, South Carolina, 1946-1952 (Box 157, Folder 22)
      April 5, 1946-April 30, 1952. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6281, Greenville, South Carolina, effective January 1, 1952
  - Sub-Series 235-6301. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6301, San Diego, California, 1946-1948 (Box 157, Folder 23)
      April 24, 1946-April 23, 1948.
  - Sub-Series 235-6302. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6302, St. Louis, Missouri, 1946-1949 (Box 157, Folder 24)
      April 24, 1946-July 25, 1949. Disbanded, effective July 25, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-6303. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6303, Mordecai Johnson Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1946-1950 (Box 157, Folder 25)
      May 1,1946-November 7, 1950. Consolidated with Lodge No. 595, Cincinnati, Ohio, effective October 1, 1950
  - Sub-Series 235-6305. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6305, Ft. Smith, Arkansas, 1946-1959 (Box 157, Folder 26)
      May 5, 1946-December 17, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6052, Little Rock, Arkansas, effective October 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-6306. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6306, Minden, Louisiana, 1946-1947 (Box 157, Folder 27)
      May 9, 1946-December 1, 1947. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1088, Shreveport, Louisiana, effective December 1, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6307. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6307, United Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1946-1959 (Box 157, Folder 28)
      May 17, 1946-December 3, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6045, St. Louis, Missouri, effective October 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-6308. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6308, Toledo, Ohio, 1946-1952 (Box 157, Folder 29)
      May 24, 1946-August 22, 1952. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1189, Toledo, Ohio, effective July 1, 1952
  - Sub-Series 235-6310. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6310, Robert Scott Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1946-1959 (Box 157, Folder 30)
      June 11, 1946-December 16, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6163, Wilmington, North Carolina, effective January 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-6311. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6311, Texarkana, Texas, 1946-1959 (Box 157, Folder 31)
      June 20, 1946-April 3, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 142, Dallas, Texas, effective January 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-6314. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6314, Fruit Growers Express Auxiliary Lodge, Baldwin, Florida, 1946-1947 (Box 157, Folder 32)
      September 5, 1946-July 27, 1947.
  - Sub-Series 235-6315. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6315, Chicago, Illinois, 1945-1947 (Box 157, Folder 33)
      January 7, 1945-October 1, 1947. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1006, Chicago, Illinois, effective October 1, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6317. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6317, Sheffield, Alabama, 1946-1960 (Box 157, Folder 34)
      October 22, 1946-August 16, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 367, Sheffield, Alabama, effective July 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-6318. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6318, Detroit, Michigan, 1946-1947 (Box 157, Folder 35)
      November 4, 1946-September 26, 1947. Suspended, effective September 26, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-6319. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6319, Pioneer Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1948-1960 (Box 157, Folder 36)
      November 10, 1948-March 24, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 124, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, no date given
  - Sub-Series 235-6320. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6320, St. John Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1946-1950 (Box 157, Folder 37)
      December 10, 1946-February 8, 1950.
  - Sub-Series 235-6321. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6321, Sutter Lodge, Sacramento, California, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 38)
      January 7, 1947-November 3, 1947.
  - Sub-Series 235-6324. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6324, Cleburne, Texas, 1947-1948 (Box 157, Folder 39)
      February 17, 1947-December 17, 1948. Disbanded, effective October 27, 1948
  - Sub-Series 235-6336. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6336, Houston, Texas, 1948-1960 (Box 157, Folder 40)
      February 5, 1948-February 2, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6051, Houston, Texas, effective January 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-6339. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6339, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1948-1960 (Box 157, Folder 41)
      November 24, 1948-April 19, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1757, Charlotte, North Carolina, effective April 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-6341. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6341, Love Lodge, Columbus, Mississippi, 1949-1960 (Box 157, Folder 42)
      November 22, 1949-June 24, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 770, Columbus, Mississippi, effective July 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-6342. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 6342, Universal Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1950-1954 (Box 157, Folder 43)
      December 1, 1950-July 24, 1954. Consolidated with Lodge No. 6062, Atlanta, Georgia, effective April 1, 1954